Guide to the Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Records ALBA.019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files, 1940-2006; 155527
  - Commemorations: Memorial Day Encampment, 1954; 155954 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Commemorations: Memorial Services, undated, 1998; 155953 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Commemorations: Memorials, 1989; 155952 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Commemorations: Monument, Barcelona, undated, 1983-1988, 2000; 155951 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Commemorations: Pennsylvania State University, Address--Robert Colodny, 1989; 155950 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Commemorations: Paul Robeson, 1998; 155949 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Commemorations: Spain, 50th Anniversary, 1986; 155948 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Commemorations: Spain, 60th Anniversary, 1996-1997; 155947 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Commemorations: Sweden, undated, 1961, 1977; 155946 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Commemorations: Union des Anciens Resistants Juifs de Belgique (Belgium), 1989; 155945 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Commemorations: Wisconsin, Madison, 1999; 155944 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain, undated, 1967, 1969; 155943 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Committees: Speakers Committee, undated; 155942 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Conference: American Continental Congress, Mexico, undated, 1949; 155941 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Conference: Asian-Pacific Peace Conference, 1952; 155940 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Conference: Canada, 1971; 155939 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Conference: Congreso Internacional de Mujeres, 1948; 155938 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Conference: Congreso Latino Americano de Juventades, undated; 155937 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Conference: Convention of Solidarity, Mexico, 1943; 155936 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Conference: Italy, 1989; 155935 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Conference: Panamericana de Solidaridad, undated; 155934 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Conference: Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB), National, 1939; 155933 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1940; 155932 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1941; 155931 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1969; 155930 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1971; 155929 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1973; 155928 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1975; 155927 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1977; 155926 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Conference: VALB, National, 1979; 155925 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Conference: VALB, National, undated; 155924 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Conference: The Worker in Spain Today, Canada, 1973; 155923 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Conference: "World Congress of Jewish Volunteers Who Fought in Spain," Israel, 1972; 155922 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Constitutions (VALB), 1939, 1941, 1973; 155921 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence: Announcements and Appeals, Friends, 1950-1984; 155920 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Announcements and Appeals, Veterans, 1938-1948; 155919 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Announcements and Appeals, Veterans, 1950-1959; 155918 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Announcements and Appeals, Veterans, 1960-1969; 155917 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Announcements and Appeals, Veterans, 1970-2000; 155916 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Announcements and Appeals, Veterans, undated; 155915 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1949; 155914 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1950; 155913 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1951-1959; 155912 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1960; 155911 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1961; 155910 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1962; 155909 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1969; 155908 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1971; 155907 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1972; 155906 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1973; 155905 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1974; 155904 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1975; 155903 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1976; 155902 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1977; 155901 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1978; 155900 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1979; 155899 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1989; 155898 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1990-2003; 155897 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, undated; 155896 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Cards and Notes, undated, 1970-1995; 155895 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Detentions, British embassy, 1942-1947; 155894 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1939-1950; 155893 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: New York Public Library, Donated Materials, 1948-1950; 155892 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Spanish Government, 1965-1978; 155891 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: United Nations, 1946-1951; 155890 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: United States Congress, 1943-1947, 1960, 1973; 155889 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: United States Department of State, 1943-1975; 155888 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: United States Post Office, 1939-1950, 1961; 155887 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: United States President, 1941-1978; 155886 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Union General de Trabajadores de Espana (UGT), 1947-1948; 155885 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Cullinen, George, 1996; 155884 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Cuba, 1948, 1976-1977, 1993; 155883 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Curriculum and Courses, undated, 1975-1979, 1992; 155882 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Curriculum and Courses: Proposal for a Center for Spanish Civil War Studies, undated; 155881 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Czech and Slovak Anti-Fascist Fighters Associations, 1990; 155880 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - DeMaio, Anthony, undated, 1942; 155879 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America, undated; 155878 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - De Vries, Lini: "Farewell U.S.A." in La Palabra y el Hombre, 1959; 155877 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Diamant, David: Jewish Volunteers, 1955, 1977; 155876 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dorland, Norman, undated, 1942-1946; 155875 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Doyle, Bob: Memoir, undated; 155874 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dua-Bogen, Gershon: Quest for Power, translation, undated; 155873 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Eby, Cecil: Between the Bullet and the Lie(review and correspondence), undated, 1970-1974; 155872 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Echeverria, Carlos Sule, 1950-1954; 155871 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Egg-Benes, Maria, undated, 1969; 155870 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Erceg, Michael: Parole, 1949; 155869 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Exhibits, undated, 1992, 1998; 155868 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Exhibits: Drew University, 1986; 155867 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Exhibits: Posters, Spanish Civil War, 1942-1944; 155866 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Exhibits: "Shouts From the Wall," Hamilton College, undated, 1997; 155865 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Ephemera: Stamps, undated; 155864 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Films, 1982; 155863 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Films: "Comrades" Film, List of Photographs for, undated; 155862 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Films: The Good Fight, undated, 1978-1984; 155861 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Films: The Good Fight, Controversy, 1986-1987; 155860 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Financial: Budgets, 1940, 1945; 155859 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Financial: Certificate of Authority for Unincorporated Association Account, 1947-1953; 155858 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Financial: Correspondence, undated, 1947-1949; 155857 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Financial: Invoices, miscellaneous, 1951-1976, 1982; 155856 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Financial: Ledger and General Journal, 1949-1953; 155855 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Financial: Payroll Books, 1946-1948; 155854 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Financial: Reports, 1940-1949; 155853 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Financial: Reports, 1948-1949; 155852 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Financial: Reports, 1971-1984; 155851 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Fisher, Harry: Comrades: Tales of a Brigadista in the Spanish Civil War, Correspondence and Reviews, undated, 1999; 155850 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Fishman, Moe, 1971-2001; 155849 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Friedman, Jack: Correspondence, 1944-1960; 155848 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Gallagher, Joe: Memoir, undated; 155847 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Gandall, William, 1946-1987; 155846 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Gandall, William: Memoir, undated, 2001; 155845 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Geiser, Carl, undated, 1989; 155844 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - German Democratic Republic, 1961; 155843 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Goldring, Ben, 1959-1980; 155842 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Albert, 1949, 1952, 1974; 155841 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Historical Commission, undated, 1968-1982; 155840 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Historical Commission: Correspondence, undated, 1975-1981; 155839 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Historical Commission: Moscow Archives, 1976-1979; 155838 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - House Committee on Un-American Activities (HUAC), 1963; 155837 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - HUAC: American Committee for the Defense of the Foreign Born, undated, 1974; 155836 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - HUAC: Committee for Democratic Rights in the U.S.A., 1962; 155835 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - HUAC: Civil Liberties, Slide Show--transcript, ca.1955; 155834 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - HUAC: Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties, Speeches, 1962, 1963; 155833 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - HUAC: Civil Rights Congress, undated, 1955; 155832 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - HUAC: Cohen, Milton, 1965-1969; 155831 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - HUAC: Committee to Abolish, 1966, 1969; 155830 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - HUAC: Committee to Defend Lincoln Veterans, Correspondence, 1951-1952; 155829 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - HUAC: Committee to Defend Lincoln Veterans, Rally, 1951-1952; 155828 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - HUAC: Committee to Defend Lincoln Veterans, Women's Committee, undated, 1952; 155827 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - HUAC: Committee to End Sedition Laws, undated, 1953-1956; 155826 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - HUAC: Defense Committees, undated, 1953; 155825 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - HUAC: Emergency Civil Liberties Committees, 1962-1965, 1972; 155824 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - HUAC: Fishman, Moe, subpoena, 1963; 155823 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - HUAC: Friends of Pete Seeger, 1961; 155822 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - HUAC: Sid, Linn, organizing, 1952; 155821 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - HUAC: Mc Neil, Allan D. (Allan Johnson), undated, 1952-1966; 155820 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - HUAC: New York Civil Rights Congress, 1951-1953; 155819 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - HUAC: Pittsburgh Civil Rights Congress, 1952-1955; 155818 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - HUAC: Pittsburgh Trial, Committee to Defend Lincoln Veterans, undated, 1951-1952; 155817 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - HUAC: Pittsburgh Trial, Correspondence--Steve Nelson, 1951-1952; 155816 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - HUAC: Pittsburgh Trial, Defense Committee, undated, 1951-1952; 155815 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - HUAC: Pittsburgh Trial, Legal Documents, undated, 1950; 155814 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - HUAC: Pittsburgh Trial, Petition, undated; 155813 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - HUAC: Smith Act, 1949, 1953; 155812 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - HUAC: Smith Act: "The Case of Martha Stone", undated; 155811 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - HUAC: Subversive Activities Control Board, undated, 1955, 1968; 155810 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - HUAC: Walter-McCarran Act, Frank Bonetti, undated, 1938; 155809 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - HUAC: Walter-Mc Carran Act, Peggy Wellman Defense Committee, undated, 1955-1956; 155808 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Hutchins, Evelyn, 1977, 1981-1982; 155807 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hyde, Mark Powell (Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran and executive secretary of the Washington, D.C. Chapter of the United American Spanish Aid Committee) Letters to Sam and Fredericka Barenberg (later Fredericka Martin) (also includes one reply from Sam Barenberg), circa 1944-1946; 384331 (Box 17, Folder 1a)
  - Ilitch, General Ljubomir, 1944-1945; 155806 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - International Brigade Association (UK), 1950-2001; 155805 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - International Brigade Memorial Trust (UK), 2004-2005; 155804 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - International Brigades, undated; 155803 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - International Brigades: 35th Anglo-American Battery, undated; 155802 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - International Brigades: Amicale des Anciens Volontaires de l' Espagne Republicaine, 1956, 1958; 155801 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - International Brigades: Asociación Brigadas Internacionales, 1992; 155800 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - International Brigades: Australian Veterans, 1965; 155799 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - International Brigades: Botwin Veterans (Poland), undated, 1972; 155798 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - International Brigades: Clippings, undated, 1996-1999; 155797 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - International Brigades: La Comision de Homenaje, undated, 1980, 1994-1999; 155796 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - International Brigades: Committee of Social Help, 1970; 155795 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - International Brigades: Conference, report, undated; 155794 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - International Brigades: Czechoslovakian Veterans, 1990, 1996; 155793 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - International Brigades: Italian Volunteers, undated; 155792 (Box 17, Folder 15a)
  - International Brigades: MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1972-2004; 155791 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - International Brigades: MacKenzie-Papineau Batallion, News Bulletin, 1976-1995; 155790 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - International Brigades: Poland, Veterans' Benefits, undated, 1970-1972, 1990-1991; 155789 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - International Brigades: Reunion, 40th-Florence, Italy, 1976; 155788 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - International Brigades: Spanish Citizenship, 1996; 155787 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - International Brigades: Sociedad Francisco Javier Mina, Mexico, 1949; 155786 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - International Brigades: Soviet Veterans, undated, 1975-1977, 1985-1988; 155785 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - International Brigades: Veterans' Food Packages, Europe, ca.1946-1948; 155784 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - International Front against Torture, undated; 155783 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1977; 155782 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Kee, Salaria (a.k.a. Salaria Kea) by James Yates, undated; 155781 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1947; 155780 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Kish, Leslie: Memoir, Dispute, undated, 1991; 155779 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Kramer, Jacob, 1988-1990; 155778 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Kranes, Louis, 1967-1969; 155777 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Landis, Arthur, 1976-1977; 155776 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Landis, Arthur: Spain! The Unfinished Revolution, correspondence, 1972; 155775 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Landis, Arthur: "The United States of America and the Cause of the Spanish Republic," draft, undated; 155774 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Lawsuit: VALB v. Eric Bernay et al., 1947; 155773 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Lending, Ed, 1993-1999; 155772 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Lists: 711 Group of the 95th Street Food Conspiracy, undated; 155771 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Lists: Fellows and Sponsors, Potential, undated; 155770 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Lists: Mailing, undated, 1951, 1952; 155769 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Lists: Mailing, 1998; 155768 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Lists: Mailing, undated; 155767 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Lists: Mailing, International, undated, 1952; 155766 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Lists: Mailing Labels, undated; 155765 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Lists: Photographs, undated; 155764 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Lists: Veterans, undated; 155763 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Lists: VALB, 1998; 155762 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Lustgarten, Larry, 1944; 155761 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Martin, Fredericka, undated; 155760 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Martin, Fredericka: Correspondence, 1970-1986; 155759 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Maki, Martin, 1973-1980; 155758 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Matson, Eric: Foster Care of Eric, Jr., 1948; 155757 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Mayer, Pablo, undated, 1990; 155756 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - McCarthy, Bill, 1950; 155755 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Medem, Gina: "Roofs of New York" (excerpt, translation), undated; 155754 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Mexico, 1944, 1961, ca.1963; 155753 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Middle East, undated, 1970, 1984; 155752 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Middle East: Gulf War, 1990-1991; 155751 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Miller, Israel Jack, v. the United States: Bail, 1940; 155750 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Mooney, Tom, 1938, 1941; 155749 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - National Board, 1939-1948; 155748 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - National Board, 1967-1969; 155747 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - National Board, 1970-1975; 155746 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - National Board, 1976; 155745 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - National Board, 1977; 155744 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - National Board, 1978; 155743 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - National Board, 1979; 155742 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - National Board, 1980; 155741 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National Board, 1982; 155740 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - National Board, 1984; 155739 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - National Board, 1985; 155738 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - National Board, 1987; 155737 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - National Board, 1989; 155736 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Board, undated; 155735 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - National Board: Administrative Committee, 1977-1981; 155734 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - National Board: Executive, 1972-1990; 155733 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - National Board: Executive, Minutes, 1942-1947; 155732 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - National Board: "Minutes Charter Constitution Finances", 1939-1941; 155731 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - National Board: Resident, Minutes, 1973-1977; 155730 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1972, 1987; 155729 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Negrin, Juan, undated, 1941; 155728 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Nelson, Cary: Madrid 1937, draft, undated; 155727 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Nelson, Cary: Madrid 1937, script, 1996; 155726 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Nelson, Cary: Essay on Edwin Rolfe, undated, 1989; 155725 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Nelson, Steve, undated, 1953-1956, 1994; 155724 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Neugass, James: "They Will Come Back", undated; 155723 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Nicaragua, undated, 1985-1991; 155722 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - North, Joe: "A Strange American Story," draft, undated; 155721 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - O' Casey, Sean, 1980; 155720 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - O' Casey, Sean: Correspondence, 1957, 1960; 155719 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Office File, undated, 1941-1948; 155718 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Office File: Certificates of Incorporation, 1939-1954; 155717 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Parker, Dorothy: Appeal, Dec 27, 1944; 155716 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Parker, Max: Al Tosca Diana: Songs From a Franco Prison, undated, 2003; 155715 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Passports: Correspondence, 1937-1944, 1948; 155714 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Poland, undated, 1977, 1983; 155713 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Posts: Bay Area, 1937-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1-14, Box OS009, Folder 1)
  - Posts: Bay Area, undated, 1952-1956, 1974-2000; 155712 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Posts: Bay Area, Anniversaries, 1982-2003; 155711 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Posts: Bay Area, Correspondence, undated, 1949-1978; 155710 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Posts: Bay Area, "Postscript to a War: Voices of the Lincoln Brigade", 1995; 155709 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Posts: Chicago, undated; 1941-1952; 155708 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Posts: Chicago, 1995-2003 (Box 27, Box 28)
  - Posts: Chicago Friends of the Lincoln Brigade, undated, 1998-2000; 155707 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Posts: Los Angeles, undated; 1952-1985; 155706 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Posts: New York, undated, 1972-1985; 155705 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Posts: New York, Permits and Licenses, 1940-1951; 155704 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Posts: Pennsylvania, Delaware Valley, 1975-1979; 155703 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Posts: South Florida, undated, 1976-1978; 155702 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1940-1949; 155701 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1950-1956; 155700 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, undated, 1960-1985; 155699 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases: "Statesments" [sic], 1919-1941; 155698 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Bulletin, 1976; 155697 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Publications: No Pasaran!, Spanien Kaempfer, 2004-2006; 155696 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Servicio de Prensa, Jun 1973-Nov 1973; 155695 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Volunteer for Liberty, 1949; 155694 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Volunteer for Liberty, Orders, 1949; 155693 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Volunteer for Liberty, Orders--Colleges, 1949-1952; 155692 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Volunteer for Liberty, Orders--Public Libraries, 1949; 155691 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rico: Vieques, 2000; 155690 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Ragner, Albin C., undated, 1982, 1989; 155689 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rauschwald, Mark, 1963-1971; 155688 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Raven, Bob: Rehabilitation, 1942-1949; 155687 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Reed, Bob, undated, 1977-1999; 155686 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Reunion: Spain, 1977; 155685 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Reunion: Spain, 1982-1983; 155684 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Reunion: Spain, 1988; 155683 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Reunion: Spain, 1996-1997; 155682 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Reunion: Spain: Clippings, 1977; 155681 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Reunion: Spain: Clippings, 1986-1988; 155680 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Rodriquez, Julius: National Desertion Bureau, 1946; 155679 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Rolfe, Edwin: The Lincoln Battalion, German Translation, undated; 155678 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor: Correspondence, 1943, 1951, 1960-1961; 155677 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Ryan, Frank, 1944, 1951; 155676 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Ryan, William G.: "I Fought in Spain," in Scribner's Commentator, 1941; 155675 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Sanchez, Pablo Guaelpo, 1950; 155674 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Sender, Andrea (Sister Benedicta), undated, 1982-1984; 155673 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Sarbaugh, Thomas: Spanish Civil War Music, 1999-2000; 155672 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Sennett, Bill, 1972-1997; 155671 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Shirai, Jack, undated, 1984-1985; 155670 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Smith, Randall (Pete), 1977-1980; 155669 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Randall (Pete): Communist Party, Controversy, 1976; 155668 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Smith, Randall (Pete): Interview, Transcript, undated; 155667 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Sossenko, George, 1988, 1996-1997; 155666 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Spain: Agencia de Prensa Espana Popular (APER), Newsletter, 1973; 155665 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Spain: Articles and Reports, 1940s; 155664 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Spain: Articles and Reports, 1960s; 155663 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Spain: Articles and Reports, 1970s; 155662 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Spain: Articles and Reports, 1980s; 155661 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Spain: Articles and Reports, Informaciones y Documentacion sobre Espana, 1975; 155660 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Spain: Asociacion de Ex-Presos y Represaliados Politicos, 1980-1985; 155659 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Spain: Basque, undated, 1970; 155658 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Spain: Catalonia, politics and protest, undated, 1976-1990; 155657 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Spain: Clippings, 1942-1959; 155656 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Spain: Clippings, undated, 1966-1995; 155655 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Spain: Comite d' Information et de Solidarite avec l' Espagne (C.I.S.E.), undated, 1973, 1975; 155654 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Spain: Committee for a Democratic Alternative in Aragon, 1973; 155653 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Spain: Communism, Clippings, undated, 1960-1984; 155652 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Spain: Communist Party (P.C.E.), undated, 1971-1975, 1979; 155651 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Spain: Des Amis de l' Espagne Republicaine, 1952, 1978-1979; 155650 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Spain: Dissident Groups, undated, 1960-1967; 155649 (Box 19, Folder 58)